<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Windows Defender Hardening on simeononsecurity</title><link>/tags/windows-defender-hardening/</link><description>Recent content in Windows Defender Hardening on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/windows-defender-hardening/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Harden Windows with Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC)</title><link>/github/windows-defender-application-control-hardening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-application-control-hardening/</guid><description>Windows-Defender-Application-Control-Hardening Harden Windows with Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC)
A list of scripts and tools this collection utilizes: MicrosoftDocs - WDAC-Toolkit Additional configurations were considered from: Microsoft - Recommended block rules Microsoft - Recommended driver block rules Microsoft - Windows Defender Application Control Explanation: Default Policies: The &amp;ldquo;Default&amp;rdquo; policies use only the default features available in the WDAC-Toolkit. Recommended Policies: The &amp;ldquo;Recommended&amp;rdquo; policies use the default features as well as Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s recommended blocks and driver block rules.</description></item><item><title>Automating the Windows Defender STIG</title><link>/github/windows-defender-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-stig-script/</guid><description>STIGS/SRGs Applied: Windows Defender Antivirus V1R9 Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:
.\sos-windowsdefenderstig.ps1</description></item><item><title>Hardening Windows Defender</title><link>/github/windows-defender-hardening/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-hardening/</guid><description>What does this script do? Enables Cloud-delivered Protections Enables Controlled Folder Access Enables Network Protections Enables Intrusion Prevention System Enables Windows Defender Application Control Policies Enables Windows Defender Attack Surface Reduction Rules Enables Windows Defender Exploit Protections Implements all requirements listed in the Windows Defender Antivirus STIG Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item></channel></rss>