<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How To Automate Windows STIG on simeononsecurity</title><link>/tags/how-to-automate-windows-stig/</link><description>Recent content in How To Automate Windows STIG on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 11:59:03 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/how-to-automate-windows-stig/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>STIGing Standalone Windows Systems</title><link>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-systems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 11:59:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-systems/</guid><description>STIGing Standalone Windows 10 Systems Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
We are seeking help with the following .Net issue
Introduction: Windows 10 is insecure operating system out of the box and requires many changes to insure FISMA compliance. Organizations like Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended and required configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system and ensure government compliance.</description></item><item><title>Optimize, Harden, and Debloat Windows 10 Deployments</title><link>/github/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 20:15:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</guid><description>Optimize, Harden, and Debloat Windows 10 Deployments Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
We are seeking help with the following .Net issue
Introduction: Windows 10 is an invasive and insecure operating system out of the box. Organizations like PrivacyTools.io, Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system. These changes cover a wide range of mitigations including blocking telemetry, macros, removing bloatware, and preventing many digital and physical attacks on a system.</description></item><item><title>STIGing Standalone Windows Servers</title><link>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-servers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-servers/</guid><description>STIGing Standalone Windows Servers Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
Introduction: Windows Server 2012, 2016, and 2019 are insecure operating systems out of the box and requires many changes to insure FISMA compliance. Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended and required configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system and ensure government compliance. These changes cover a wide range of mitigations including blocking telemetry, macros, removing bloatware, and preventing many physical attacks on a system.</description></item></channel></rss>