<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Automation on simeononsecurity</title><link>/tags/automation/</link><description>Recent content in Automation on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Optimize and Debloat Windows 10 Deployments</title><link>/github/windows-optimize-harden-debloat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-optimize-harden-debloat/</guid><description>Windows-Optimize-Debloat For those who seek to minimize their Windows 10 installs.
Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
Introduction: Windows 10 is an invasive and insecure operating system out of the box. Organizations like Microsoft, PrivacyTools.io, and others have recommended configuration changes to optimize and debloat the Windows 10 operating system. These changes are include blocking telemetry, deleting logs, and removing bloatware to name a few. This script aims to automate the configurations recommended by those organizations.</description></item><item><title>GLVK Auto Install Script for KMS Activation</title><link>/github/kms-auto-ps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/kms-auto-ps/</guid><description>SimeonOnSecurity - KMS-Auto-PS GLVK Auto Install Script for KMS Activation
Recommened Reading: Microsoft - KMS Client Keys (GLVK) How to run the script: Manual Install: If manually downloaded, the script must be launched from an administrative powershell in the directory containing all the files from the GitHub Repository
Set-ExecutionPolicy -ExecutionPolicy RemoteSigned -Force Get-ChildItem -Recurse *.ps1 | Unblock-File .\sos-kmsglvkactivationauto.ps1</description></item><item><title>Harden Windows with Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC)</title><link>/github/windows-defender-application-control-hardening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-application-control-hardening/</guid><description>Windows-Defender-Application-Control-Hardening Harden Windows with Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC)
A list of scripts and tools this collection utilizes: MicrosoftDocs - WDAC-Toolkit Additional configurations were considered from: Microsoft - Recommended block rules Microsoft - Recommended driver block rules Microsoft - Windows Defender Application Control Explanation: XML vs. BIN: Simply put, the &amp;ldquo;XML&amp;rdquo; policies are for applying to a machine locally and the &amp;ldquo;BIN&amp;rdquo; files are for enforcing them with either Group Policy or Microsoft Intune.</description></item><item><title>VirusTotal PowerShell Modules</title><link>/github/virustotal-ps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/virustotal-ps/</guid><description>A collection of PowerShell Modules for Interacting with the VirusTotal API
Notes:
You&amp;rsquo;ll need your VirusTotal API key, which can be found on your Shodan Account Examples of the APIs used in the modules may be found on the VirusTotal Developers Page Download and Install Download the modules from the GitHub Repository Install all the modules Get-ChildItem -Recurse *.ps1 | Import-Module</description></item><item><title>Hardening Windows Systems with Applocker</title><link>/github/applocker-hardening/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/applocker-hardening/</guid><description>Ultimate Applocker Hardening Configuration Script.
What does this script do? Locks down system resources to bare minumum needed for basic OS functionality Recommended reading: api0cradle/UltimateAppLockerByPassList) Microsoft Recommended Block Rules MotiBa/AppLocker NSA Cyber Bitlocker Gidance Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:
.\sos-applockerhardening.ps1</description></item><item><title>Hardening Windows Terminals. Command Prompt and PowerShell</title><link>/github/windows-terminal-hardening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-terminal-hardening/</guid><description>Scripts and Documentation for Hardening Windows Command Prompt and PowerShell
What does this script do? Disables Command Prompt Disables PowerShell v2 Disables WSMAN and PSRemoting Enables PowerShell Constrained Language Mode Enables PowerShell Logging Recommended Reading: PowerShell Best Practices PowerShell Constrained Language Mode Securing PowerShell in the Enterprise Windows Defender Hardening Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>Shodan Powershell Modules</title><link>/github/shodan-powershell/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 19:34:03 -0600</pubDate><guid>/github/shodan-powershell/</guid><description>Shodan_PS A collection of PowerShell Modules for Interacting with the Shodan API
Notes:
You&amp;rsquo;ll need you Shodan API key, which can be found on your Shodan Account Examples of the APIs used in the modules may be found on the Shodan Developers Page Certain Modules may use scan or query credits Query Credits are used when you download data via the website, CLI or API (what these scripts do). Since we are using the API it is important to note that query credits are deducted if: A search filter is used Page 2 or beyond is requested The credits renew at the start of the month and 1 credit lets you download 100 results.</description></item><item><title>Automating the Windows Defender STIG</title><link>/github/windows-defender-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-stig-script/</guid><description>STIGS/SRGs Applied: Windows Defender Antivirus V1R9 Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:
.\sos-windowsdefenderstig.ps1</description></item><item><title>Hardening Windows Defender</title><link>/github/windows-defender-hardening/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-hardening/</guid><description>What does this script do? Enables Cloud-delivered Protections Enables Controlled Folder Access Enables Network Protections Enables Intrusion Prevention System Enables Windows Defender Application Control Policies Enables Windows Defender Attack Surface Reduction Rules Enables Windows Defender Exploit Protections Implements all requirements listed in the Windows Defender Antivirus STIG Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>STIG Compliant GPOs and Importing them into a Windows Domain</title><link>/github/stig-compliant-domain-prep/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:13:17 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/stig-compliant-domain-prep/</guid><description>STIG Compliant Domain Prep Import all the GPOs provided by SimeonOnSecurity to assist in making your domain compliant with all applicable STIGs and SRGs.
Notes: This script is designed for use in Enterprise environments
STIGS/SRGs Applied: Windows 10 V1R23
Windows Defender Antivirus V1R9
Windows Firewall V1R7
Internet Explorer 11 V1R19
Adobe Reader Pro DC Continous V1R2
Adobe Reader Pro DC Classic V1R3</description></item><item><title>Adobe Reader DC STIG Script</title><link>/github/adobe-reader-dc-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 16:50:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/adobe-reader-dc-stig-script/</guid><description>Automate Adobe Reader Pro DC STIG Apply the Adobe Reader Pro DC STIGs in one simple script.
Notes: This script is designed for use in Enterprise environments and will insure 100% compliance with the applicable stigs.
STIGS/SRGs Applied: Adobe Reader Pro DC Continous V1R2
Adobe Reader Pro DC Classic V1R3
Download the script: You may download the script from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be launched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>STIGing Standalone Windows Systems</title><link>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-systems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 11:59:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-systems/</guid><description>STIGing Standalone Windows 10 Systems Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
We are seeking help with the following .Net issue
Introduction: Windows 10 is insecure operating system out of the box and requires many changes to insure FISMA compliance. Organizations like Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended and required configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system and ensure government compliance.</description></item><item><title>Dot NET STIG Script</title><link>/github/dot-net-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 22:14:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/dot-net-stig-script/</guid><description>Automate the .NET Framework 4 STIG Applying the .NET STIG is definitely not straightforward. For many administrators it can take hours to fully implement on a single system. This script applies the required registry changes and modifies the machine.config file to implement FIPS and other controls as required.
Work in Progress
DO NOT APPLY IN PRODUCTION
Notes: This script can not and will not ever get the .NET stig to 100% compliance.</description></item><item><title>FireFox Privacy Script</title><link>/github/firefox-privacy-script/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 03:32:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/firefox-privacy-script/</guid><description>FireFox Privacy Script Organizations like PrivacyTools.io and ffprofile have suggested changes to make FireFox more secure and private. These changes cover suggested browser extentions, blocking telemetry, disabling 3rd-party cookies, disabling trackers, etc.
This script will take the pregenerated FireFox configuration files and install them in the proper directories on a Windows system.
Download the required files Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>FireFox STIG Script</title><link>/github/firefox-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 19:17:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/firefox-stig-script/</guid><description>FireFox STIG Script The Firefox V4R29 isn&amp;rsquo;t the easiest of STIGs to apply. This script will implement most of the required FireFox policies. In the future, the FireFox ADMX templates and GPO&amp;rsquo;s will be applied in this script.
Work In Progress
Download the required files Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>Windows 10 Branding</title><link>/github/windows-10-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 14:37:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-10-branding/</guid><description>Setup branding on Windows 10 and Server 2016/2019 Systems Many organizations have a need or want to control the branding of a Windows system. This includes the desktop wallpaper, the users avatar, the Windows lock screen, and sometimes the OEM Logo. In Windows 10, Windows Server 2016, and Windows Server 2019 this is not particularly easy. But, with the aide of the linked script, we can partially automate it and make the process much easier.</description></item><item><title>Automating Oracle JRE 8 STIG</title><link>/github/oracle-jre-8-stig/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:54:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/oracle-jre-8-stig/</guid><description>Automate Oracle JRE 8 STIGS The Oracle JRE STIGs aren’t so straight forward, requiring administrators to research JAVA documentation and generate java config files, when most administrators are used to solely STIG-ing using group policy.
Download the required files Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
STIGS/SRGs Applied: Oracle JRE 8 V1R5 Sources: MyITGuy - deployment.properties
cbu.edu - Java Technotes
How to run the script The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>Hardening Apache Web Server</title><link>/github/hardening-apache/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:15:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>/github/hardening-apache/</guid><description>A collection of example configurations and scripts to aid system administrators in hardening Apache web servers. Apache, out of the box, is surprisingly insecure. Many best practices and security configurations have to be configured manually before rolling Apache out in a production environment. You may use this GitHub repository as a starting point towards securing your Apache instances.
Installing ModSecurity with OWASP Core Rule Set Step 1: Update Repositories On Ubuntu/ Debian:</description></item><item><title>Optimize, Harden, and Debloat Windows 10 Deployments</title><link>/github/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 20:15:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</guid><description>Optimize, Harden, and Debloat Windows 10 Deployments Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
We are seeking help with the following .Net issue
Introduction: Windows 10 is an invasive and insecure operating system out of the box. Organizations like PrivacyTools.io, Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system. These changes cover a wide range of mitigations including blocking telemetry, macros, removing bloatware, and preventing many digital and physical attacks on a system.</description></item><item><title>Automating Windows Updates with Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdate, and Startup Scripts</title><link>/github/automating-windows-updates-with-chocolatey-pswindowsupdate-and-startup-scripts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 17:46:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>/github/automating-windows-updates-with-chocolatey-pswindowsupdate-and-startup-scripts/</guid><description>Automating Windows Updates with Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdate, and Startup Scripts Download all supporting files from the GitHub Repository
 In today&amp;rsquo;s modern workplace environment, system administrators constantly are battling for time. Rolling out the latest Windows updates can be extremely time consuming taking up to a week given enough systems. Along with some assistance from Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdates, and Startup Scripts, Systems Administrators can roll out update with as little as a single reboot of each machine.</description></item><item><title>Windows Spectre Meltdown Mitigation Script</title><link>/github/windows-spectre-meltdown-mitigation-script/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-spectre-meltdown-mitigation-script/</guid><description>https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4073119/protect-against-speculative-execution-side-channel-vulnerabilities-in Simple script to implement protections against speculative execution side-channel vulnerabilities in Windows systems.
Microsoft is aware of a new publicly disclosed class of vulnerabilities that are called “speculative execution side-channel attacks” and that affect many modern processors including Intel, AMD, VIA, and ARM.
Note: This issue also affects other operating systems, such as Android, Chrome, iOS, and macOS. Therefore, we advise customers to seek guidance from those vendors.
We have released several updates to help mitigate these vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title>STIGing Standalone Windows Servers</title><link>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-servers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/stiging-standalone-windows-servers/</guid><description>STIGing Standalone Windows Servers Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
Introduction: Windows Server 2012, 2016, and 2019 are insecure operating systems out of the box and requires many changes to insure FISMA compliance. Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended and required configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system and ensure government compliance. These changes cover a wide range of mitigations including blocking telemetry, macros, removing bloatware, and preventing many physical attacks on a system.</description></item></channel></rss>