<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>simeononsecurity</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 18:31:06 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HackTheBox - Challenges - Crypto - Bank Heist</title><link>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-bank_heist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 18:31:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-bank_heist/</guid><description>HackTheBox - Challenges - Crypto - Bank Heist Provided Files: For this challenge you&amp;rsquo;re provided with the following cipher text:
444333 99966688 277733 7773323444664 84433 22244474433777, 99966688 277733 666552999. 99966688777 777744277733 666333 84433 443344477778 4447777 44466 99966688777 4466688777733. 84433 5533999 8666 84433 55566622255 4447777 22335556669. 4666 8666 727774447777. 47777888 995559888 4555 47777888 44999988 666555997 : 8555444888477744488866888648833369!! Walk Through: Very clearly, this is either a T9 or Multitap cipher.
Multitap is the cipher in this instance though.</description></item><item><title>HackTheBox - Challenges - Crypto - Call</title><link>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-call/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 18:31:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-call/</guid><description>HackTheBox - Challenges - Crypto - Call Provided Files: You are provided one file:
sound.mp3 Walk Through: Playing the sound.mp3, you&amp;rsquo;ll hear a familiar sound. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar the sounds you&amp;rsquo;re hearing are hearing DTMF (dual tone multi frequency) tones. The same tones you used to hear while dialing on a pay phone or while getting through automated teller menus.
Each tone has a specific frequency. You could get the numbers manually, but who has the time for that?</description></item><item><title>HackTheBox - Challenges - Crypto - Decode</title><link>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-decode/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 16:57:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-decode/</guid><description>HackTheBox - Challenges - Crypto - Decode Provided Files: In this challenge you are provided two strings of information.
993gmULBNujjrZCDev3W8kAVaLkXiyHhCL3500188bA= and
gAAAAABboRUb0FsuiYBk1tsXRDr6KAzU1xrNSUv7grB-G-dAEeyqj99kUebz466I2VcH5xDa5HEc5KkbgTklQ7tm9JCRPlJtRng1Ns3VEvbrk7B835OINfPnRbc-UIOnnCmW3CgMdMtf5wGLN299AZEzxIvuy71WC5d9xJDchyiORycuzCth95-4nTKphlNQQ2ko3DX72RxWeEjwt3mavnFXqcOCkGxUhJYmFltz_6ND56VGTrXZi_CK5xLODOX4sj1GNwN_CrU3sJ0obTdA2wF5OaDZLbA1GBPfK0PDlC9WxoUf85K0tFXKfqbt3c5YqtqfytNG5gTkbDFM2NjE7BveBf1DP9ca8g== Walk Through: At first glance it appears this is some sort of key and some cipher text. After searching around, you&amp;rsquo;ll find that it is a Fernet cypher. Asecuritysite.com has a great tool to decode it for you.
The plain text from the above information gives you a base64 encoded string</description></item><item><title>STIG Compliant GPOs and Importing them into a Windows Domain</title><link>/posts/stig-compliant-domain-prep/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:13:17 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/stig-compliant-domain-prep/</guid><description>STIG Compliant Domain Prep Import all the GPOs provided by SimeonOnSecurity to assist in making your domain compliant with all applicable STIGs and SRGs.
Notes: This script is designed for use in Enterprise environments
STIGS/SRGs Applied: Windows 10 V1R23
Windows Defender Antivirus V1R9
Windows Firewall V1R7
Internet Explorer 11 V1R19
Adobe Reader Pro DC Continous V1R2
Adobe Reader Pro DC Classic V1R3</description></item><item><title>Adobe Reader DC STIG Script</title><link>/posts/adobe-reader-dc-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 16:50:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/adobe-reader-dc-stig-script/</guid><description>Automate Adobe Reader Pro DC STIG Apply the Adobe Reader Pro DC STIGs in one simple script.
Notes: This script is designed for use in Enterprise environments and will insure 100% compliance with the applicable stigs.
STIGS/SRGs Applied: Adobe Reader Pro DC Continous V1R2
Adobe Reader Pro DC Classic V1R3
Download the script: You may download the script from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be launched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>STIGing Standalone Windows Systems</title><link>/posts/stiging-standalone-windows-systems/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 11:59:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/stiging-standalone-windows-systems/</guid><description>STIGing Standalone Windows 10 Systems Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
We are seeking help with the following .Net issue
Introduction: Windows 10 is insecure operating system out of the box and requires many changes to insure FISMA compliance. Organizations like Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended and required configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system and ensure government compliance.</description></item><item><title>Dot NET STIG Script</title><link>/posts/dot-net-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 22:14:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/dot-net-stig-script/</guid><description>Automate the .NET Framework 4 STIG Applying the .NET STIG is definitely not straightforward. For many administrators it can take hours to fully implement on a single system. This script applies the required registry changes and modifies the machine.config file to implement FIPS and other controls as required.
Work in Progress
DO NOT APPLY IN PRODUCTION
Notes: This script can not and will not ever get the .NET stig to 100% compliance.</description></item><item><title>FireFox Privacy Script</title><link>/posts/firefox-privacy-script/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 03:32:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/firefox-privacy-script/</guid><description>FireFox Privacy Script Organizations like PrivacyTools.io and ffprofile have suggested changes to make FireFox more secure and private. These changes cover suggested browser extentions, blocking telemetry, disabling 3rd-party cookies, disabling trackers, etc.
This script will take the pregenerated FireFox configuration files and install them in the proper directories on a Windows system.
Download the required files Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>FireFox STIG Script</title><link>/posts/firefox-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 19:17:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/firefox-stig-script/</guid><description>FireFox STIG Script The Firefox V4R29 isn&amp;rsquo;t the easiest of STIGs to apply. This script will implement most of the required FireFox policies. In the future, the FireFox ADMX templates and GPO&amp;rsquo;s will be applied in this script.
Work In Progress
Download the required files Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>Windows 10 Branding</title><link>/posts/windows-10-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 14:37:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/windows-10-branding/</guid><description>Setup branding on Windows 10 and Server 2016/2019 Systems Many organizations have a need or want to control the branding of a Windows system. This includes the desktop wallpaper, the users avatar, the Windows lock screen, and sometimes the OEM Logo. In Windows 10, Windows Server 2016, and Windows Server 2019 this is not particularly easy. But, with the aide of the linked script, we can partially automate it and make the process much easier.</description></item><item><title>WMI Filters</title><link>/posts/wmi-filters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 13:35:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/wmi-filters/</guid><description>WMI Filters A collection of WMI filters to assist with Windows Group Policy deployments
When deploying GPOs, Microsoft reccomends to use WMI filters to speed up the process and isolate policies in large domains. WMI Filters allow you to specify GPOs down to a specific piece of software or Windows version with the potential to get significantly much more complex. The linked GitHub Repository includes some of the most commonly used WMI filters so that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to create them.</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions</title><link>/termsandconditions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 15:31:48 -0500</pubDate><guid>/termsandconditions/</guid><description>Terms and Conditions Welcome to SimeonOnSecurity!
These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of SimeonOnSecurity&amp;rsquo;s Website, located at https://SimeonOnSecurity.com.
By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use SimeonOnSecurity if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: &amp;ldquo;Client&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Your&amp;rdquo; refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacypolicy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 15:24:07 -0500</pubDate><guid>/privacypolicy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy for SimeonOnSecurity&amp;lt; At SimeonOnSecurity, accessible from https://SimeonOnSecurity.ch, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by SimeonOnSecurity and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in SimeonOnSecurity.</description></item><item><title>Automating Oracle JRE 8 STIG</title><link>/posts/oracle-jre-8-stig/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:54:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/oracle-jre-8-stig/</guid><description>Automate Oracle JRE 8 STIGS The Oracle JRE STIGs aren’t so straight forward, requiring administrators to research JAVA documentation and generate java config files, when most administrators are used to solely STIG-ing using group policy.
Download the required files Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
STIGS/SRGs Applied: Oracle JRE 8 V1R5 Sources: MyITGuy - deployment.properties
cbu.edu - Java Technotes
How to run the script The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>Toolkit and Recommendations</title><link>/recommendations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 20:03:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s in SimeonOnSecurity&amp;rsquo;s toolkit? VPN Recommendations: Mullvad VPN
ProtonVPN
EMail Providers: ProtonMail - Preferred - E2E Encrypted EMail
Tutanota - E2E Encrypted EMail
SIP/DID Providers: VOIP.MS - Preferred
MySudo - Preferred
Google Hangouts
Messengers and SMS Providers: Signal - Preferred
Wire
Wicker
Service Providers: Abine DeleteMe - Preferred Delete your records from major data brokers</description></item><item><title>Hardening Apache Web Server</title><link>/posts/hardening-apache/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:15:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/hardening-apache/</guid><description>A collection of example configurations and scripts to aid system administrators in hardening Apache web servers. Apache, out of the box, is surprisingly insecure. Many best practices and security configurations have to be configured manually before rolling Apache out in a production environment. You may use this GitHub repository as a starting point towards securing your Apache instances.
Installing ModSecurity with OWASP Core Rule Set Step 1: Update Repositories On Ubuntu/ Debian:</description></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1350 KB4569509 DNS Server Vulnerability</title><link>/posts/cve-2020-1350_kb4569509_dns_server_vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 21:09:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/cve-2020-1350_kb4569509_dns_server_vulnerability/</guid><description>KB4569509: Guidance for DNS Server Vulnerability CVE-2020-1350 Introduction On July 14, 2020, Microsoft released a security update for the issue that is described in CVE-2020-1350 | Windows DNS Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This advisory describes a Critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability that affects Windows servers that are configured to run the DNS Server role. We strongly recommend that server administrators apply the security update at their earliest convenience.</description></item><item><title>Brave ADMX Templates</title><link>/posts/brave-admx-templates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 19:30:39 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/brave-admx-templates/</guid><description>BraveADMX Brave, as a company, has failed to release ADMX templates for the brave browser siteing pushing pure registries as the only supported option. As the Brave Browser is build off of Chromium, it should support most, if not all, the same policies from the Chromium and Google Chrome ADMX templates. With that in mind, we&amp;rsquo;ve modified the Google Chrome ADMX templates to reflect the Brave Browser&amp;rsquo;s registry path. After some initial troubleshooting and testing, the templatates seem to work.</description></item><item><title>Chromium ADMX Templates</title><link>/posts/chromium-admx-templates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 19:30:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/chromium-admx-templates/</guid><description>ChromiumADMX Proper ADMX Template for the Chromium Browser
Brave, as a company, has failed to release ADMX templates for the Chromium Browser that may be installed at the same time as the Google Chrome templates. With that in mind, we&amp;rsquo;ve modified the Google Chrome ADMX templates to reflect the Chromium Browser&amp;rsquo;s registry path and placed in tandum in the Google ADMX Folder in GPO.
These Policy Definitions are in a Pre-Alpha state.</description></item><item><title>Optimize, Harden, and Debloat Windows 10 Deployments</title><link>/posts/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 20:15:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</guid><description>Optimize, Harden, and Debloat Windows 10 Deployments Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
We are seeking help with the following .Net issue
Introduction: Windows 10 is an invasive and insecure operating system out of the box. Organizations like PrivacyTools.io, Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system. These changes cover a wide range of mitigations including blocking telemetry, macros, removing bloatware, and preventing many physical attacks on a system.</description></item><item><title>Automating Windows Updates with Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdate, and Startup Scripts</title><link>/posts/automating-windows-updates-with-chocolatey-pswindowsupdate-and-startup-scripts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 17:46:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/automating-windows-updates-with-chocolatey-pswindowsupdate-and-startup-scripts/</guid><description>Automating Windows Updates with Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdate, and Startup Scripts Download all supporting files from the GitHub Repository
 In today&amp;rsquo;s modern workplace environment, system administrators constantly are battling for time. Rolling out the latest Windows updates can be extremely time consuming taking up to a week given enough systems. Along with some assistance from Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdates, and Startup Scripts, Systems Administrators can roll out update with as little as a single reboot of each machine.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>What is SimeonOnSecurity?
 SimeonOnSecurity (SOS) is a security and automation blog that's goal is to bring you all the behind the scenes technical content not normally found online. This blog serves as Simeon's show of work and his all around enthusiasm for the field.
Who is Simeon?
 Simeon is a Systems Administrator by day and Cyber Security and Privacy Enthusiast by night. He is a tinkerer, a hobbyist, and all around geek and nerd.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>/contactus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contactus/</guid><description>
Contact Details
SimeonOnSecurity does not have publicly available contact details at this time.
You may follow our RSS feed or our GitHub at this time.
Discord Server</description></item><item><title>HackTheBox - Challenge - Crypto - Weak RSA</title><link>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-weak_rsa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/writeups/hackthebox-challenges-crypto-weak_rsa/</guid><description>HackTheBox - Challenge - Crypto - Weak RSA The HTB &amp;ldquo;Weak RSA&amp;rdquo; Crypto is an easy challenge based on the RSA cipher.
Provided Files: You are provided with the following files:
flag.enc key.pub Walk-through: At first glance, you&amp;rsquo;d think you can decrypt the flag with the public key.
For that, we might use the OpenSSL package to decrypt the flag. This time it&amp;rsquo;s a bit different and you&amp;rsquo;ll find that the OpenSSL package won&amp;rsquo;t work for this challenge.</description></item><item><title>HackTheBox - Invite Challenge</title><link>/writeups/hackthebox-invite-challenge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/writeups/hackthebox-invite-challenge/</guid><description>HackTheBox - Invite Challenge What is Hack the Box ? HackTheBox is an online platform to test and advance your skills in penetration testing and cyber security.
How do you join Hack the box ? To create an account on HackTheBox (HTB) you have to complete the invite challenge, or hack yourself the way in. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry though it isn&amp;rsquo;t hard and this article will aid you incompleting the challenge.</description></item><item><title>STIGing Standalone Windows Servers</title><link>/posts/stiging-standalone-windows-servers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/stiging-standalone-windows-servers/</guid><description>STIGing Standalone Windows Servers Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
Introduction: Windows Server 2012, 2016, and 2019 are insecure operating systems out of the box and requires many changes to insure FISMA compliance. Microsoft, Cyber.mil, the Department of Defense, and the National Security Agency have recommended and required configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system and ensure government compliance. These changes cover a wide range of mitigations including blocking telemetry, macros, removing bloatware, and preventing many physical attacks on a system.</description></item></channel></rss>