<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recommendations on simeononsecurity</title><link>/recommendations/</link><description>Recent content in Recommendations on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/recommendations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recommended Anti-Virus</title><link>/recommendations/anti-virus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/anti-virus/</guid><description>Rankings are based on SimeonOnSecurity&amp;rsquo;s professional opinion and basic testing against malicious samples provided by VirusTotal. These recommendations do not take into account vendors privacy policies or related practices and only cover the AV capabilities, detection, user experience, and performance.
Notes:
Generally speaking, AV is not required on Linux or MacOS. It is not recommended to use any VPN or password manager thay may be provided with the AV suite.</description></item><item><title>Recommended Books</title><link>/recommendations/books/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/books/</guid><description>Educational: Automate the Boring Stuff with Python - Al Sweigart Blue Team Field Manual - Alan J White CCNA Routing and Switching Portable Command Guide - Scott Empson Extreme Privacy - Michael Bazzell Hash Crack - Joshua Picolet Linux Command Line and Shell Scripting Bible - Richard Blum and Christine Bresnahan Linux Pocket Guide - Daniel J. Barrett Make Your Own Living Trust - Denis Clifford Attorney Open Source Intelligence Techniques - Michael Bazzell Operator Handbook - Joshua Picolet Practical Ansible 2 - Daniel Oh Practical Network Automation - Abhishek Ratan Python Crash Course - Eric Matthes Red Team Field Manual - Ben Clark The Art of Deception - Kevin Mitnick The Art of Intrusion - Kevin Mitnick The Art of Invisibility - Kevin Mitnick The Hacker Playbook 3 - Peter Kim This Book Was Self-Published - Michael Bazzell Tribe of Hackers - Marcus J.</description></item><item><title>Recommended Browser Plugins</title><link>/recommendations/browser_plugins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/browser_plugins/</guid><description>Note: The only daily-driver browser I recommend is FireFox. Alternatively you should be using the TOR Browser. Do not install plugins in the TOR browser.
U-Block Origin - Prefered - A great Open-Source AD blocker. HTTPS Everywhere - Prefered - Forces your browser to load sites over HTTPS rather than HTTP Decentraleyes - Local CDN Emulator ClearURLs - Dynamically removes tracking tags from links CanvasBlocker - Prevents JavaScript Fingerprinting Multi Account Containers - Allows for isolated brower sessions Terms of Service, Didn&amp;rsquo;t Read - Informs user of shady ToS Bitwarden - Secure Open-Source Cloud Password Manager Privacy Badger - Learns and blocks trackers</description></item><item><title>Recommended eMail Providers</title><link>/recommendations/email/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/email/</guid><description> ProtonMail - Preferred - E2E Encrypted EMail
Tutanota - E2E Encrypted EMail</description></item><item><title>Recommended Every Day Carry (EDC)</title><link>/recommendations/edc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/edc/</guid><description>The typical every day carry (EDC) consists of a few basic tools. Typically, those are a knife or blade, a flashlight, a watch, and a pen. I&amp;rsquo;ll recommend a few in different price points within their categories with a few extras below.
Knife/Blades: CRKT Squid Folding Pocket Knife - $15 Gerber EAB Pocket Knife - $18 Kershaw Leek - $55 Spyderco Tenacious - $55 TPT Slide - $85 Spyderco Para Military 2 - $165 Kizer Cutlery Begleiter Folding Pocket Knife - $169 Flashlights: RovyVon A1 - $28 Streamlight 88039 ProTac - $30 Olight S2 Cree XM-L2 - $49 OLIGHT S2R II - $55 Olight Warrior - $80 Watches: AURSINC WiFi Deauther Wristband - $50 Timex Men&amp;rsquo;s Expedition Scout 40 - $50 Orient Bambino - $100 Orient Mako II - $120 Suunto Core - $120 Nixon Regulus SS - $200 Casio Men&amp;rsquo;s Pro Trek PRW-3500T-7CR - $269 Suunto Core, Brushed Steel - $280 Casio Men&amp;rsquo;s Pro Trek PRW-50T-7ACR - $300 Bulova Moonwatch - $510 Pens: Zebra Pen F-301 - $20/12 Zebra Pen 29411 F-701 $8 Fisher Space Pen Bullet Pen - $25 Fisher Space AG7 Original Astronaut Space Pen - $50 BIG IDEA DESIGN Ti Arto EDC - $95 Ti Ultra Pen - $250 Extra: Bags/Backpacks: 5.</description></item><item><title>Recommended Hacker Hardware</title><link>/recommendations/hacker_hardware/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/hacker_hardware/</guid><description>CanaKit Raspberry Pi 4
AURSINC WiFi Deauther Watch ESP8266
Alfa Long-Range Dual-Band AC1200 2.4GHz/5GHz
GlobalSat BU-353-S4 USB GPS Receiver
Proxmark3 V3.0 ID DEV Kits M1
HackRF One
RTL-SDR RTL2832U
BaoFeng BF-F8HP
GL.iNet GL-AR750S-Ext
Protectli Vault 4 Port, Firewall Micro Appliance/Mini PC
YubiKey 5 NFC
GoTrust Idem Card - FIDO2 &amp;amp; U2F BLE and NFC Security Key</description></item><item><title>Recommended Learning Resources</title><link>/recommendations/learning_resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/learning_resources/</guid><description>General Information Technology: Cybrary - A great, mostly free, cyber and IT learning resource. LinkedIn Learning - a general learning platform. (Check with your school, they might offer free membership) Pluralsight - Preferred a general learning platform with High Quality video content. (Check with your school, they might offer a free membership. Udemy - a general learning platform. Cyber Security: CyberWarfare (Red and Purple-Team Labs and Certifications) HackTheBox - Black-Box CTF Challenges (Has paid membership) INE - Free, and Paid, High Quality Cyber Security labs and training Immersive Labs - Free Cyber Security Labs (Free for active students)(Has paid offerings) Mosse Cyber Security Institute - Free Cyber Security Labs (Has paid offerings) PenTesterLab - Hands on Pentesting Labs (Has paid offerings) TryHackMe - Guided CTF challenges.</description></item><item><title>Recommended Messengers</title><link>/recommendations/messengers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/messengers/</guid><description> Signal - Preferred
Wire
Wicker</description></item><item><title>Recommended Privacy Resources</title><link>/recommendations/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/privacy/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Privacy is a fundamental right, and essential to democracy, liberty, and freedom of speech. Our privacy is being abused by governments (with mass-surveillance), corporations (profiting from selling personal data), and cyber criminals (stealing our poorly-secured personal data and using it against us). Security is needed in order to keep your private data private, and good digital security is critical to stay protected from the growing risks associated with the war on data.</description></item><item><title>Recommended Services</title><link>/recommendations/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/services/</guid><description>Privacy Services: Abine DeleteMe - Preferred Delete your records from major data brokers OneRep- Alternate Delete your records from major data brokers Masking Information: Abine Blur - Alternate Password manager, identity masking, and one-time-use debit cards Privacy.com - Preferred - Generate one-time-use debit cards Online Password Managers: BitWarden - Preferred - E2E Encrypted Online Password Manager</description></item><item><title>Recommended Stand-Alone Headsets</title><link>/recommendations/headsets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/headsets/</guid><description>Preferably purchased with a headphone DAC like the FiiO E10K or FiiO K3 Below $100
$50 | Audio-Technica ATH M20x
$70 | Audio-Technica ATH M30x
$99 | Audio-Technica ATH M40x
$65 | Philips SHP9500
$100-$300
$149 | Audio-Technica ATH M50x
$145 | Philips Audio Fidelio X2HR
$149 | beyerdynamic DT 770 PRO</description></item><item><title>Recommended Stand-Alone Microphones</title><link>/recommendations/microphones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/microphones/</guid><description>Below $100
$80 | Samson Q2U Below $500
$200 | Samson Q2U+ Focusrite Scarlett Solo (3rd Gen)
$325 | Samson Q2U + GoXLR Mini
Below $1500
$1300 | Shure SM7B Cardioid Dynamic Microphone + RODE PSA 1 Swivel Mount Studio Microphone Boom Arm + Cloud Microphones Cloudlifter CL-1 Mic Activator + GoXLR - Mixer, Sampler, &amp;amp; Voice FX
$1400 | Electro-Voice RE20 Broadcast Announcer Microphone with Variable-D + Electro-Voice 309A + RODE PSA 1 Swivel Mount Studio Microphone Boom Arm + Cloud Microphones Cloudlifter CL-1 Mic Activator + GoXLR - Mixer, Sampler, &amp;amp; Voice FX</description></item><item><title>Recommended VOIP Providers</title><link>/recommendations/voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/voip/</guid><description> VOIP.MS - Preferred
MySudo - Preferred
Google Hangouts</description></item><item><title>Recommended VPN Providers</title><link>/recommendations/vpns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/vpns/</guid><description> Mullvad VPN
ProtonVPN</description></item><item><title>Recommended Webcams</title><link>/recommendations/webcams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/recommendations/webcams/</guid><description> $99 | Logitech C922x Pro Stream Webcam
$160 | Logitech BRIO
$170 | Logitech StreamCam</description></item></channel></rss>