<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on simeononsecurity</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:15:03 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hardening Apache Web Server</title><link>/posts/hardening-apache/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:15:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/hardening-apache/</guid><description>
A collection of example configurations and scripts to aid system administrators in hardening Apache web servers. Apache, out of the box, is surprisingly insecure. Many best practices and security configurations have to be configured manually before rolling Apache out in a production environment. You may use this GitHub repository as a starting point towards securing your Apache instances.
Installing ModSecurity with OWASP Core Rule Set Step 1: Update Repositories On Ubuntu/ Debian:</description></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1350 KB4569509 DNS Server Vulnerability</title><link>/posts/cve-2020-1350_kb4569509_dns_server_vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 21:09:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/cve-2020-1350_kb4569509_dns_server_vulnerability/</guid><description>
KB4569509: Guidance for DNS Server Vulnerability CVE-2020-1350 Introduction On July 14, 2020, Microsoft released a security update for the issue that is described in CVE-2020-1350 | Windows DNS Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This advisory describes a Critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability that affects Windows servers that are configured to run the DNS Server role. We strongly recommend that server administrators apply the security update at their earliest convenience.</description></item><item><title>Brave ADMX Templates</title><link>/posts/brave-admx-templates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 19:30:39 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/brave-admx-templates/</guid><description>
BraveADMX Proper ADMX Templates for the Brave Browser
These Policy Definitions are in a Pre-Alpha state. They should be used for testing purposes only
Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
Modified Google Chrome Policy Definitions according to: Brave Group Policy
Note: Replaced &amp;ldquo;HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\Software\Policies\Google\Chrome&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\Software\Policies\BraveSoftware\Brave&amp;rdquo;
How to install 1.) Copy all files except readme.md to &amp;ldquo;C:\Windows\PolicyDefinitions&amp;rdquo; and/or &amp;ldquo;\\domain.tld\domain\Policies\PolicyDefinitions&amp;rdquo; 2.) Profit?</description></item><item><title>Chromium ADMX Templates</title><link>/posts/chromium-admx-templates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 19:30:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/chromium-admx-templates/</guid><description>
ChromiumADMX Proper ADMX Template for the Chromium Browser
These Policy Definitions are in a Pre-Alpha state. They should be used for testing purposes only
Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
Modified Google Chrome Policy Definitions according to: Chromium Policy Templates
Note: Replaced &amp;ldquo;HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\Software\Policies\Google\Chrome&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\Software\Policies\Chromium&amp;quot;
How to install 1.) Copy all files except readme.md to &amp;ldquo;C:\Windows\PolicyDefinitions&amp;rdquo; and/or &amp;ldquo;\\domain.tld\domain\Policies\PolicyDefinitions&amp;rdquo; 2.) Profit?</description></item><item><title>Optimizing and Hardening Windows 10 Deployments</title><link>/posts/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 20:15:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/optimizing-and-hardening-windows10-deployments/</guid><description>
Optimizing and Hardening Windows 10 Deployments Download all the required files from the GitHub Repository
Windows 10 is an invasive and insecure operating system out of the box. Organizations like PrivacyTools.io, Microsoft and the Department of Defense have recomended configuration changes to lockdown, harden, and secure the operating system. These changes cover a wide range of mitigations including blocking telemetery, macros, removing bloatware, and preventing many physical attacks on a system.</description></item><item><title>Automating Windows Updates with Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdate, and Startup Scripts</title><link>/posts/automating-windows-updates-with-chocolatey-pswindowsupdate-and-startup-scripts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 17:46:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/automating-windows-updates-with-chocolatey-pswindowsupdate-and-startup-scripts/</guid><description>
Automating Windows Updates with Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdate, and Startup Scripts Download all supporting files from the GitHub Repository
 In today&amp;rsquo;s modern workplace environment, system administrators constantly are battling for time. Rolling out the latest Windows updates can be extremely time consuming taking up to a week given enough systems. Along with some assistance from Chocolatey, PSWindowsUpdates, and Startup Scripts, Systems Administrators can roll out update with as little as a single reboot of each machine.</description></item></channel></rss>