<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GPO on simeononsecurity</title><link>/tags/gpo/</link><description>Recent content in GPO on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:13:17 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/gpo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>STIG Compliant GPOs and Importing them into a Windows Domain</title><link>/posts/stig-compliant-domain-prep/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:13:17 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/stig-compliant-domain-prep/</guid><description>STIG Compliant Domain Prep Import all the GPOs provided by SimeonOnSecurity to assist in making your domain compliant with all applicable STIGs and SRGs.
Notes: This script is designed for use in Enterprise environments
STIGS/SRGs Applied: Windows 10 V1R23
Windows Defender Antivirus V1R9
Windows Firewall V1R7
Internet Explorer 11 V1R19
Adobe Reader Pro DC Continous V1R2
Adobe Reader Pro DC Classic V1R3</description></item><item><title>WMI Filters</title><link>/posts/wmi-filters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 13:35:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/wmi-filters/</guid><description>WMI Filters A collection of WMI filters to assist with Windows Group Policy deployments
When deploying GPOs, Microsoft reccomends to use WMI filters to speed up the process and isolate policies in large domains. WMI Filters allow you to specify GPOs down to a specific piece of software or Windows version with the potential to get significantly much more complex. The linked GitHub Repository includes some of the most commonly used WMI filters so that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to create them.</description></item><item><title>Brave ADMX Templates</title><link>/posts/brave-admx-templates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 19:30:39 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/brave-admx-templates/</guid><description>BraveADMX Brave, as a company, has failed to release ADMX templates for the brave browser siteing pushing pure registries as the only supported option. As the Brave Browser is build off of Chromium, it should support most, if not all, the same policies from the Chromium and Google Chrome ADMX templates. With that in mind, we&amp;rsquo;ve modified the Google Chrome ADMX templates to reflect the Brave Browser&amp;rsquo;s registry path. After some initial troubleshooting and testing, the templatates seem to work.</description></item><item><title>Chromium ADMX Templates</title><link>/posts/chromium-admx-templates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 19:30:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/chromium-admx-templates/</guid><description>ChromiumADMX Proper ADMX Template for the Chromium Browser
Brave, as a company, has failed to release ADMX templates for the Chromium Browser that may be installed at the same time as the Google Chrome templates. With that in mind, we&amp;rsquo;ve modified the Google Chrome ADMX templates to reflect the Chromium Browser&amp;rsquo;s registry path and placed in tandum in the Google ADMX Folder in GPO.
These Policy Definitions are in a Pre-Alpha state.</description></item></channel></rss>