<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blue-Team on simeononsecurity</title><link>/tags/blue-team/</link><description>Recent content in Blue-Team on simeononsecurity</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/blue-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hardening Windows Systems with Applocker</title><link>/github/apache-hardening/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/apache-hardening/</guid><description>Ultimate Applocker Hardening Configuration Script.
What does this script do? Locks down system resources to bare minumum needed for basic OS functionality Recommended reading: api0cradle/UltimateAppLockerByPassList) Microsoft Recommended Block Rules MotiBa/AppLocker NSA Cyber Bitlocker Gidance Download the required files Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:
.\sos-applockerhardening.ps1</description></item><item><title>Hardening Windows Terminals. Command Prompt and PowerShell</title><link>/github/windows-terminal-hardening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-terminal-hardening/</guid><description>Scripts and Documentation for Hardening Windows Command Prompt and PowerShell
What does this script do? Disables Command Prompt Disables PowerShell v2 Disables WSMAN and PSRemoting Enables PowerShell Constrained Language Mode Enables PowerShell Logging Recommended Reading: PowerShell Best Practices PowerShell Constrained Language Mode Securing PowerShell in the Enterprise Windows Defender Hardening Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item><item><title>Automating the Windows Defender STIG</title><link>/github/windows-defender-stig-script/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-stig-script/</guid><description>STIGS/SRGs Applied: Windows Defender Antivirus V1R9 Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:
.\sos-windowsdefenderstig.ps1</description></item><item><title>Hardening Windows Defender</title><link>/github/windows-defender-hardening/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/github/windows-defender-hardening/</guid><description>What does this script do? Enables Cloud-delivered Protections Enables Controlled Folder Access Enables Network Protections Enables Intrusion Prevention System Enables Windows Defender Application Control Policies Enables Windows Defender Attack Surface Reduction Rules Enables Windows Defender Exploit Protections Implements all requirements listed in the Windows Defender Antivirus STIG Download the required files: Download the required files from the GitHub Repository
How to run the script: The script may be lauched from the extracted GitHub download like this:</description></item></channel></rss>